

Andrea Delli

MSc student & Al Engineer

- **Q** +39 3780 633 433
- Turin, Italy
- andrea.delli2001@gmail.com

- morplussign.github.io
- github.com/RonPlusSign
- in linkedin.com/in/andrea-delli

ABOUT ME

I'm a master's student in Artificial Intelligence and Data Analytics at the Polytechnic of Turin, with a focus on generative AI and an interest in robotics. I have hands-on experience as a full-stack developer for healthcare solutions, and I'm currently exploring agentic systems and multimodal LLM integrations.

I coordinate a team of developers within a university student team, where we design and build a space-exploration rover to compete in international robotics competitions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Al Engineer & Full Stack Developer, Genomedics S.r.l.

10/2020 - present

Development of web platforms for pre-processing, big data analysis, advanced data extraction and indicators in the medical field.

Use of LLM agents for automated decision support, with RAG and monitoring of costs.

Technologies used: Python, Angular, Laravel, SQL

Software Engineer, Team DIANA - Polytechnic of Turin

10/2023 - present

Coordinator of a developer group of the DIANA Student's Team for the development of a rover for space missions, with a focus on sensor fusion, positional tracking and creation of a simulation environment.

Technologies used: C++, Python, C#, Unity

• Web Developer, ITIS A. Meucci

2018-2020

Creation of an innovative website for the management and interactive display of school timetables and teacher substitutions (scuolafacile.itismeucci.it)

Technologies used: Vue.js, PHP

Internship, SeSa s.p.a.

5/2019

Training course focused on the design and implementation of web platforms for big data analysis through dynamic dashboards. Independent study of methods for creating mobile apps.

Technologies used: Tableau, Flask, Flutter

EDUCATION

Master's Degree in Artificial Intelligence and Data Analytics, Polytechnic of Turin

10/2023 - present

Advanced training in machine learning, deep learning, natural language processing (NLP), computer vision and big data analytics. Deepening of reinforcement learning techniques, blockchain and mobile application development, with a focus on advanced AI models, including large language models. Current GPA: 28.6/30

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering, University of Florence

8/2020 - 9/2023

Final mark: 110/110 with honors

Thesis: "Analysis and evolution of a software for constrained and dynamic routing on mobility data in a Smart City" (github.com/RonPlusSign/whatif-router)

I.T. Diploma, ITIS A. Meucci, Florence

8/2015 - 6/2020

Final mark: 100/100

CyberChallenge, University of Florence

2/2019 - 5/2019

First Italian cybersecurity training program with courses on cybersecurity and ethical hacking for talented young people from high schools and universities.

PROJECTS

 LLMs4Subjects: LLM-based Automated Subject Tagging for a National Technical Library's Open-Access Catalog Large Language Models

Domain Randomization Techniques for Reinforcement Learning:
Bridging the Reality Gap

Reinforcement Learning

• Chronos for Multivariate Time Series Forecasting of Financial Data

Deep Natural Language Processing

Real-Time Anomaly Segmentation for Road Scenes

Computer Vision

Rust back-up tool for emergency situations

System and device programming

Quoridor game for LandTiger board

Computer Architectures

WorkStream: a mobile app for teamwork management

Mobile Application Development

TECH STACK

Coding

Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, C++, C, Rust, SQL, Java, Kotlin, HTML, CSS

Frameworks

Angular, Laravel, PyTorch, Android, Django, MongoDB, Node.js, Vue.js

Other

Linux (full-time user), Git, Docker, Arduino, Notion, LaTeX, Digital photography, Photoshop

CERTIFICATES

Cambridge B2 FCE (ID: C4570374) Final Score: 182 (CEFR Level: C1)

ICDL exams (ID: IT 2308571)

Computer Essentials, Online Essentials, Word Processing, IT-Security, Online Collaboration

LANGUAGES

Italian, native speaker

English, professional working proficiency

I authorize the processing of personal data present in the CV according to the Regulation of the European Parliament 679/2016.